Guide to the Carla Stellweg Papers M1752
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Gallery Shows, Curatorial Work and Other Professional Activities
  - Johannesberg Bienale- Atrikus correspondence, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Salon [N?] Colombia - Jury Colcultura, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - (Ltr) recommend Gerardo Mosquera New Museum, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Grant to do research D.C., Fondo Del Sol etc., 1994 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Berlin: Hausder Kulturen der Welt - "Symposium Marco Polo Syndrome", 1995 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Monterrey, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Pepon Osorio Coco Fusgo Latino Mtg @ Exit Art, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Foto Septiembre - Other engagement - Panel "Transnational Photography", 1996 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Bienal Ceramica Grupo Alfa Monterrey - (Traveled to do studio visits-recommend.), 1997 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - "Domestic Partnerships: New Impluses in Decorative Arts from the Americas" (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Panel C.A.A. "New Spaces of Identity w/ Victor Zamudio Taylor", 1997 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Ana Pellicer - Advice, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - San Antonio Museum of Art, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Hunter - Studio crit., 1999 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - SAMA Collection talk for docents, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - [Label] (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - [Exhibition invitations] (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - [Exhibition invitations] (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - [Exhibition invitations] (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - [Exhibition invitations - Blue Star] (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - [Exhibition invitations - Blue Star] (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - [Exhibition invitations - Blue Star] (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - [Exhibition invitations - Blue Star] (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - [Exhibition invitations - Carla Stellweg Gallery] (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - [Exhibition invitations - Stellweg Seguy Gallery] (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - [Exhibition invitations - White Box] (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - [White Box fundraising invitations] (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Cuba related docs, 1981-1996 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Invites + small pamphlets, 1983-1995 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - R. Weiss/art historian, 1989-1997 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Other info re Cuban art inside-outside, 1990-1992 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Cuba press articles, 1990-2000 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - [Cuba - New Art Examiner] (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Giulio Blanc re: Cuban art, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Memoria Project, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - J.R. Wolin, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - M. Sanchez y Cuba - J.M. Fors, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Wiegersma secondary market, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Wiegersma secondary market, 1992-1994 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Tjerk Wiegersma - Wiegersma Fine Art - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Tjerk Wiegersma - Brussels Gallery - Correspondence, 1994, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Secondary market - Baghoomian, Wiegersma, etc. - Nosei, Shafrazi - S. Ala, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Baghoomian bankruptcy, 1992-1993 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Anderson - Basquiat - Vrej Baghoomian Gallery, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Consignments, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - Consignments, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - 5/6/7/8 Bway Space Gallery receipts - Expenses, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - 9/10/11/12 Bway Gallery Space receipts - Expenses, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Wiegersma, Anderson, Baghoomian bankruptcy - [Label] (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Auction market news, 1990-2003 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Latino art market press backdrop, 1990s (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - [Label] (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Basel Art Fair, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - C.S. Gal to Sotherby's - Alberto Barral - Educational Studies Group @ Gallery 1991 - Alfonso Dau, Guadalajara collector, media entrepreneur [includes negatives], 1991-1993 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Miami Art Fair, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - C.S. rejected by Arco-American - U.S. special selection + others: profiled as this or that issue identity & nationality, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Fial - Brussels Foire Internationale D'Arts Latin American [includes slides], 1994 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Miami Art Fair, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Miami Art Fair, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Art Nexus, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Miami Art Fair, 1995-1996 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Guadalajara Art Fair - Farco + Fitac [includes slides], 1995 Jun (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - International Forum of Contemporary Art Theory (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Expoarte Guadalajara (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Art Fair, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Gramercy Art Fair - Sta Fe, N.M. [includes photographs and negatives], 1995 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Gramercy NYC + Miami, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Arco - Madrid, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Arco - Purchase, Luis Camnitzer, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Arco - Madrid, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - [Arco '97], 1997 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Arco '97 Art Fair Madrid, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Reina Sofia acquisition M. De Latore, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - 1 of C. Stellweg Gallery's locations - Loft on 87 East Houston Street (other location Stellway-Seguy Gellery - Macer St. Soho + CS Gallery Broadway + Prince St. Soho) [includes photographs] (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - [NY Art Book Fair], 2009 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - [Kell Munoz Wigodsky] (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - [Miscellaneous] (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - [Gallery sign in book] (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - [Gallery sign in book] (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - [Gallery sign in book] (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - The Latin American Spirit - 1) General background 2) Research biblio-artists exhibits/etc, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - The Latin American Spirit press kit (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - [Mexico: Splendors of Thirty Centuries] (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Analysis pad [Stellway-Seguy Gallery ledger] (Flat-box 92, Folder 1)
  - Stellweg Seguy Gallery advertisments (Flat-box 92, Folder 6)
  - Revelaciones (Flat-box 93, Folder 5)
  - Oitcica Clarke, Pape [Helio Oiticica] (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - [The Broken Line] (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - ["Lucha Libre"] (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - ["Poesia cruda y peluda..."] (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Press BAW/TAF Lace Linea Quebra, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - [Postcards and ephemera] (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - [Letter from Pilar "Anarca" Rodriguez] (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - [Pins by Alfredo Jaar for "Dialogues of Peace" show] (Box 101, Item 1)
  - [Art piece (artifact)] (Box 101, Item 2)
  - Miscellaneous exhibition invites and brochures, 1982-2007 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Miscellaneous exhibition invites and brochures from some of the galleries Carla Stellweg was associated with including: Carla Stellweg Gallery, Stellweg-Seguy Gallery, Blue Star Art Space and White Box, among others. The artists represented in the brochures include: Jesse Amado, Blade, Lola Alvarez Bravo, Luis Camnitzer, Carlos Capelan, Monica Castillo, Arturo Elizondo, Carlos Garaicoa, Maria Elena Gonzalez, David Lamelas, Luz Maria Gordillo, David Mach, David Moreno, Jaime Palacios, Tatiana Parcero, Liliana Porter, Juan Sanchez, Eugenia Vargas, Kukuli Velarde and others.
- Series 3. Frida Kahlo Exhibits
  This series documents the gallery exhibit The Camera Seduced: Portraits of Frida Kahlo, which led to publication of a book of the same name. Starting as a gallery exhibit, the show traveled to 12 venues worldwide. In addition to information about the exhibition, the series contains research for the show, including newspaper clippings.
  - Frida Kahlo: negatives of work (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Chronicle Books, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Libro/Book (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Frida Kahlo: The Camera Seduced (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Background, significant photography, 1987-1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Research photos: Frida Kahlo, 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Loan agreement and consignment forms (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Fotofolio: Portraits of Frida and friends, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Frida Kahlo: sales and invoices, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Frida press: show and book, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - J. Martin Gallery, Frida Kahlo show: purchases, correspondence, etc., 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence re. Frida Kahlo, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - L. Bloch - Frida Kahlo, 1990-1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Frida - Bernard Silberstein, 1990-1994 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Book Lookout, New York, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Cristina Kahlo, Antonil Kahlo, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Fritz Henle - Frida Kahlo, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Book production, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - L. Derijcke Imschoot - La Chambre publishers, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Frida Kahlo show at Jan Baum Gallery, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Frida Kahlo - Japan show, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Frida Kahlo - Japan show, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Alejandr Matiz /Leo Matiz - Frida Kahlo, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Chronicle Books (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Cenidiap rejects: Frida Kahlo (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Florence Arquin: Frida foto research, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Frida Kahlo show, Tokyo, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - C. Madrazo: Frida Kahlo show, Mexico, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Sozzani, Milan: Frida Kahlo show, 1992-1995 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Galerie Quintessens, Frida show, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Barcelona show, Frida Kahlo, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Frida Kahlo Mexico show, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Frida show, Bass Museum of Art, canceled, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Frida fotos: copyright, etc., 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Frida show, MFA Houston, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - N. Muray, Nina Muray, 1994-1996 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - M. Zamora: research and show in Frida traveling exhibitions, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Frida Show: SUNY New Paltz, College Art Gallery, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Frida Kahlo show, Argentina, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Frida Kahlo and Women Photographing Women, 1999-2000 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Frida Kahlo slides (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Frida Kahlo Japanese exhibit photograph album (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Frida Kahlo newspaper articles (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Frida Kahlo newspaper articles (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Frida Kahlo newspaper articles (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Frida Kahlo newspaper articles (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Articles/scholars re. Frida Kahlo (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding Frida Kahlo (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Loan agreements for Frida Kahlo exhibits (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - [Frida Kahlo exhibition invitations] (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Art Nexus [reviews of The Camera Seduced] (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - [Frida Kahlo by Magail Lara] (Flat-box 93, Folder 1)
- Series 4. Articles, Reviews, and Other Writing
  This series contains files on Stellweg's articles, reviews and other written works. Materials include correspondence, typescripts, and publications containing articles by Stellweg. Such publications include Vie Des Arts, Vanguard, Art Nexus, ARTnews, as well as various artist books and catalogs. Information on The Camera Seduced: Portraits of Frida Kahlo can be found in Series 3. Frida Kahlo Exhibits. Some of Stellweg’s articles may also be found in Series 5. Publications.
  - Vie Des Arts -Canada 1968 pre Olympics Mexico + 1982 aspects of cont. Mex art, 1968-1983 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Vargas - Gutierrei los compadres, 1974-1994 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Regina Vater background Laica, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Vanguard Magazine - C.S. text, 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Coloquio Internacional Xalapa, U.N.A.M. lusti investigaciones Esletices 1982 publication (Iconografia en el Arte Contemporaneo), 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Art en Colombia - Art Nexus, Celia Birbragher etal - Published and advertised, 1979-1994 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Art Nexus [with articles by Stellweg] (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Fotographia contemporanea txt, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - ARTnews cover + article Carla post-Franco Spanish artists, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Txt cat./I. Vargas, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - CS txt A. Colunga + E. Sullivan review article, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Les Levine cat. txt, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Text for Mex. photography book, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - +-0 mag. texts - Belgium Bill Lundberg, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - J.L. Cuevas txt, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Jan Hendrix text-book, 1980-1994 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Carla edited English transl. cont. art from Netherlands Moca, Chicago, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - [Label] (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - ARTnews reviews, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Magenta mag. Guadalajara hx, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - J. Torres-Garcia txt-cat., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Franklin Furnace mag. flue - txt. C. Stellweg, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Aqui cat + text Fisher Art Gallery, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Chicano related S.F.: Sapa + Intar: N.Y., 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - My + others txts re. fantastic/Hispanic exhibits, 1986-1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Review mag N.Y. Americas society C.S. article neo Mexican artists, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - L.A. art mag - My article (art market, etc.), 1988-1990 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Txt Alt. Museum show + catalogue, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Colombia art show - My cat. + text, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Interview R. Welch, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Gildemontes txt L.A. Municipal Art Gallery, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Arlington Museum of Art - "Spanish Remnants" [includes slides], 1992 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Txt dig. revolution Carla -> Pedro Mexer, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Txt Jaime Palacios CS + Givlio Blanc, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Art Nexus article - Helio Oiticica, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Heresies - Latina voices Carla, Kukuli V., M.E. Gimenez, Ana Mendietz - CS Gallery P.R., 1993 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - C.S. txt Bronx-Border-Immigrant Show, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - M. Lara cat txt, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Havana biennial text, cat, lecture, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Printed copy - Bienal de Habana - Catalog, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Txt cat. L. Johnson Show - Cam, Hstn, Tx, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - My Council for the Humanities presentation text, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Yasmin Ramirez - Domestic Partnership Show @ Art in General, wrote text cat + panel w/ V.Z.T., E. Sullivan, et al, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Txt Axtlan Reina Sofia Show, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - A. Cruzvillegas - A. Lopez txt - snow angel - 1990-1997 was staff @ gallery, 1990-2000 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - "Domestic Partnerships" Carla's text at Art in General (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - NY Arts - C.S. article C. Jimenez/Gabriel Orozco, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Txt Venice Biennale E. Vargas, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - +-0 (Plus, Minus, Zero) [with article by Stellweg] (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Series 5. Publications
  Series 5 contains two subseries. The first subseries, Related to Exhibits and Artists, contains art magazines and exhibition catalogs, including the autographed catalogs of several artists. Many of these publications are marked with notes, often indicating an article that relates to Stellweg or an artist involved with her gallery. Publications and art catalogs from Blue Star Art Space and White Box can be found in this subseries. A full run of Artes Visuales, a magazine which Stellweg founded and edited, is included. Other publications include Excelsior, Atlantica, Vie des Arts, and Art Nexus.
  The second subseries, Consultation and Research, is comprised of publications which were used as research for Stellweg’s consultation work, writing, and other professional activities.
  This series is arranged alphabetically within the two subseries.
  - Related to Exhibits and Artists
    - Acts of Obsession (1), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Acts of Obsession (2), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Acts of Obsession (3), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Acts of Obsession (4), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Alejandro Colunga, 1966-86 [with invitation to Monterrey show, signed and dedicated to Carla and Roger, with color crayon drawing] (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Anos de Ausencia 10 Fernando Gamboa (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Art & Auction, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Arte Internacional, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 1-4) (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 5-8) (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 9-12) (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 13-16) (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 17-20) (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 21-24) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Artes Visuales (vols. 22-28) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Art exhibition catalogs (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Art exhibition catalogs (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Art exhibition catalogs (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Art exhibition catalogs and ephemera (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Art exhibition catalogs and ephemera (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Art exhibition catalogs and ephemera (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Art exhibition catalogs: group shows (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Art exhibition catalogs: group shows (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Art exhibition catalogs: group shows (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Art exhibition catalogs: group shows (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Artforum, 1984 Oct, 1985 Jan (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Art in America, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Art Magazine, 1988 May (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Art magazines (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ARTnews, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - ARTnews, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - ARTnews, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Art Nexus, 1992 Apr (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Art Nexus, 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Art Nexus, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Art Nexus, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Art Nexus, 2001 Jan (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Art Nexus/Exhibition review, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Atlantica, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Atlantica, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Atlantica, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Atlantica, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Atlantica, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Atlantica, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Atlantica, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Atlantica, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Atlantica, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Atlantica, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - The Autobiography and Sex Life of Andy Warhol (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Autographed, dedicated catalogs - Alejandro Aguilera (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Autographed, dedicated catalogs - Ciudad - Luis Fernando Pelaez, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Autographed, dedicated catalogs - Cronicas de viaje - Luis Fernando Pelaez, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Autographed, dedicated catalogs - Fanny Sanin: At the Edge (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Autographed, dedicated catalogs - Maripaz Jaramillo Serie Caribe (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - BAW/TAF [Border Art Workshop/Taller de Art Fronterizo] (Box 98)
    - "The Bleeding Heart", 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Blue Star advertisment + other non-profits (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 71-11, Folder 11)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - [Blue Star publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Crash Brochure (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Crash, graffiti art (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cross Currents: Bookworms from the Edge of the Pacific (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Details, 1985 Mar (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Dibujo, 1986 (Flat-box 95, Folder 1)
    - El Oficio (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Esquire: The Great Art of the 70's, 1974 May (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Excelsior, 1968-1969 (Flat-box 94, Folder 2)
    - Excelsior, 1970 (Flat-box 94, Folder 3)
    - Excelsior, 1971-1973 (Flat-box 94, Folder 4)
    - Exhibit catalogs (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Flash Art, 1983 Nov, 1984 Jun (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Fotofest, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Fotofest, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Fotofest, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Fotofest, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Fotografia (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti art (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - "Grand Street #61", 1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Grand Street, #62", 1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - The Gynecologist by Joan Lyons (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Havana '95 International Mail Art Show, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Historia de una Fiesta (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - "Images of Mexico," Banamex Collection, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - The Meal by Josely Carvlho [signed] (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Multiple World: An International Surveyof Artists' Books (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Nueva Luz (Flat-box 96, Folder 3)
    - One-person Catalogues - Stellweg-Seguy Gallery - Blade and Quik (Flat-box 95, Folder 3)
    - +-0 [Plus, Minus, Zero] (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - "Point Counter Point," Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Poliester (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Poliester vol 5, #17 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - [Publications and catalogs, including Bimbo Dirt, New York Graffiti, Artforum, and Mira] (Flat-box 95, Folder 2)
    - Revista, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - "The Rio Grande - My Berlin Wall," Michael Tracy, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Second Thoughts by Ulises Carrion (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Travesia de la Escritura (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Umbrella (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Valuable, unique originals - Out of print/rare - Contrabienal [MICLA] (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Valuable, unique originals - Out of print/rare - [MICLA] (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Various Latin American artists: group show (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Vanity Fair, 1986 Mar (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Vie des Arts, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Vie des Arts, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Vie des Arts, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Vie des Arts, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [White Box publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - [White Box publications/catalogs and related publications] (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - [White Box related publications] (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous exhibit catalogs (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous newsclippings (photocopies) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous newsclippings (photocopies) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Consultation and Research
    - Argentina (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Argentina (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Argentina (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Argentina (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Argentina (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Argentina (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Argentina (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Argentina (Box 88, Folder 2)